CONTACT



PHONE

+234 812 249 7729



MAIL

enioluwa40@gmail.com



WEBSITE

https://enioluwa.github.io/web/

PRO SKILLS

Web Design	===
UI Design	75%
UX Design	70%
Web Development	90%
Graphic design	85%
Logo design	92%
Branding strategies	85%
Project Management	85%
Illustration	75%
	80%
Problem resolution	94%
Image manipulation	85%

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator	85%
Adobe Photoshop	80%
Adobe Indesign	80%
Canva	85%
Graphic design	92%
	92%

ENIOLUWA OYEDEMI

CREATIVE DIGITAL DESIGNER



ABOUT ME

Results-oriented Digital Artist successful at applying technical skills to create art that informs and engages customers. Clear communicator and collaborative team player with an eye for detail and skill in customer relations. I am a designer with over 5 years of successful experience in digital and print design. Strengths in Adobe creative suites and a host of other design tools backed by years of personal and corporate training.



WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL DESIGNER - 08/2021 - PRESENT Foremedia Groups, London, United Kingdom.

- Designed website layouts, templates and unique branded looks.
- Aligned designs with brand image while meeting usability and website standards.
- Provided advice and guidance on aesthetics for campaigns, projects and promotional events.
- Prepared briefs for projects and presented design ideas to stakeholders.
- Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule.
- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Completed in-depth product design tests with help of different software, models and design systems.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - 09/2020-08/2021 Rasmed publications limited, Ibadan, Oyo state

- Developed creative design for marketing packages, including print materials, brochures, banners and signs.
- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.

EDUCATION

CALIFORNIA INSTITUTE OF THE ARTS

Visual Elements of User Interface Design/2021-PRESENT Online

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN

Bachelor of Science: Mathematics/ 2015-2019 Oduduwa Road, 200132, Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria

AMAZING GRACE COLLEGE

High School Diploma/ 2009-2014
Old Ife Rd, Egbeda 200113, Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria

CERTIFICATE

- LINUX PROFESSIONAL ESSENTIALS CERTIFICATE
- **CERTIFICATE OF NATIONAL SERVICE**

- Employed design fundamentals when selecting typography, composition, layout and color in design work.
- Met with customers to present mockups and collect information for adjustments.
- Cultivated positive relationships with clients by maintaining over 80% satisfaction rate.
- Developed print materials such as brochures, banners and signs.
- Created digital image files for use in digital and traditional printing methods.

DIRECTOR OF OPERATIONS - 12/2019 - 09/2020 MNG Code Academy, Ibadan, Oyo

- Produced regular reports to evaluate performance, adjust strategies and maintain agile, sustainable operations.
- Developed, ran and constantly evaluated the curriculum for the organization Code Academy.
- Developed IT projects for the trainees in the MNG Code Academy.
- Oversaw such projects and provided guidance and resources needed for trainees to achieve intended results.
- Worked with the IT Team to provide mentoring for the greenhorn trainees to design, operate and maintain technology tools/products of the organization such as Websites, Blogs, Mobile Apps, Social Media Tools etc.

DIGITAL MARKETER - 11/2018 - 04/2019 Flamation Studios, Lagos, Lagos state

- Identified growth opportunities and developed initiatives to increase market share.
- Monitored and optimized advertising campaigns using Google, Facebook, Twitter and Instagram.
- Created social media content with consistent content and tone.
- Increased customer engagement through social media.
- Developed marketing content such as blogs, promotional materials and advertisements for social media.
- Managed social media accounts for organization, generating interest for existing and upcoming product or service releases.